Inventory of O.41 - Collection of Lists and Documentation Regarding Those Who Perished and Those Who Were Persecuted During the Holocaust Period O.41
O.41 - Collection of Lists and Documentation Regarding Those Who Perished and Those Who Were Persecuted During the Holocaust Period
- Lists of Jews deported from various locations in Germany, date empty; 249 List of deportees xerox; O.41/638
  - List of Jews from Thuringia deported 10/05/1942, date empty; 249 List of deportees; O.41/638.6
    Expulsion from Germany; Apolda,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Arnstadt,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Aschenhausen,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Bad Salzungen,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Bauerbach,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Berkach (Meiningen),<>,Thuringia,Germany; Bleicherode,Erfurt,Saxony Province,Germany; Eisenach,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Erfurt,Erfurt,Saxony Province,Germany; Gehaus,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Geisa,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Gera,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Gotha,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Hildburghausen,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Ilmenau,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Altenburg,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Jena,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Kahla,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Kaltennordheim,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Meiningen,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Nordhausen,Erfurt,Saxony Province,Germany; Poessneck,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Roemhild,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Rudolstadt,<>,Thuringia,Germany; Ruhla,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Saalfeld,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Sondershausen,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Sonneberg,<>,Thuringia,Germany; Suhl,Erfurt,Saxony Province,Germany; Schleusingen,Erfurt,Saxony Province,Germany; Themar,<>,Thuringia,Germany; Tiefenort,<>,Thuringia,Germany; Walldorf,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Weimar,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Bad Liebenstein,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Eisenberg Thueringen,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Greussen,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Huepstedt ueber Dingelstadt Eichsfeld,Erfurt,Saxony Province,Germany; Kaltensundheim ueber Meiningen,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany; Moehra,Weimar,Thuringia,Germany
    List of Jews from Thuringia deported 10/05/1942
    The list/s contain approximately 723 names
  - List of Jews from Zwickau deported to Poland, 11/04/1942, Deportation von Zwickauer Juden am 11 April 1942 nach Polen; date empty; 1 List of deportees; O.41/638.7
    Expulsion from Germany; Zwickau,Zwickau,Saxony,Germany; <>,<>,<>,Poland
    List of Jews from Zwickau deported to Poland, 11/04/1942
  - List of Jews from Magdeburg and the Magdeburg vicinity deported, 13-14/04/1942 and 13/07/1942, date empty; 43 List of deportees; O.41/638.8
    Expulsion from Germany; Magdeburg,Magdeburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Aken,Merseburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Aschersleben,Magdeburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Ballenstedt,Dessau,Anhalt,Germany; Barby,Magdeburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Bernburg,Dessau,Anhalt,Germany; Burg,Magdeburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Calbe Saale,Magdeburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Dessau,Dessau,Anhalt,Germany; Egeln,Magdeburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Halberstadt,Magdeburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Jessnitz,<>,<>,Germany; Koethen,Dessau,Anhalt,Germany; Quedlinburg,Magdeburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Schoenebeck Elbe,Magdeburg,Saxony Province,Germany; Wernigerode,<>,Saxony,Germany; Zerbst,Dessau,Anhalt,Germany
    List of Jews from Magdeburg and the Magdeburg vicinity deported, 13-14/04/1942 and 13/07/1942
    The list/s contain approximately 500 names
  - List of Jews deported from Halle, 30-31/05/1942, date empty; 21 List of deportees; O.41/638.9
    Expulsion from Germany; Halle an der Saale,Merseburg,Saxony Province,Germany
    List of Jews deported from Halle, 30-31/05/1942
    The list/s contain approximately 155 names
- List of Jews from Budapest who perished during the Holocaust, prepared by Alice Ghingold, 10/11/1999-10/11/1999; 2 List of deportees List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/523
  Budapest,Pest-Pilis-Solt-Kiskun,<>,Hungary
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Ghingold Bernardne-Bucuresti,Romania
  List of Jews from Budapest who perished during the Holocaust, prepared by Alice Ghingold
- Death certificates of Mihel Sapsa and his sons Ghidale and Avram, from Iasi, who perished in Podul Iloaiei, 30/06/1941, Extras din registrul starii civile pentru morti de anul 1945; 23/11/1945-23/11/1945; 4 Personal documents Certification Photograph Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/531
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by וסרמן מלכה
  Death certificates of Mihel Sapsa and his sons Ghidale and Avram, from Iasi, who perished in Podul Iloaiei, 30/06/1941 Included in the file is a: Photograph of a mass grave in Podul Iloaie in which 12,000 Jews are buried.
- Confirmation by the military commission in the Samtredia district that Red Army soldier, Private Khaim Moshiashvili, was Missing In Action in battle, as of 12/05/1944, 14/06/1972-14/06/1972; The file was created by הקומיסריון הצבאי; 2 Personal documents Certification Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/667
  Jewish soldiers in the Red Army; Samtredia,Samtredia,<>,Georgia (USSR); the Soviet armed forces,<>,<>,<>
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by מושיאשוילי אליהו
  Confirmation by the military commission in the Samtredia district that Red Army soldier, Private Khaim Moshiashvili, was Missing In Action in battle, as of 12/05/1944
- Confirmation by the ITS regarding the fate of Charles Skekely, born in Budapest, who was an inmate in Auschwitz, 1943-1944 and perished in Buchenwald, 09/02/1945, 04/04/1990-04/04/1990; 1 Personal documents Certification Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/527
  Nice,Alpes Maritimes,<>,France; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland; Buchenwald,Camp; Budapest,Pest-Pilis-Solt-Kiskun,<>,Hungary
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by שקל גבריאל
  Confirmation by the ITS regarding the fate of Charles Skekely, born in Budapest, who was an inmate in Auschwitz, 1943-1944 and perished in Buchenwald, 09/02/1945
- List of Jews designated for deportation from Hannover to Riga, 15/12/1941, date empty; 30 List of deportees xerox; O.41/539
  Deportation of German Jews; Hannover,Hannover,Hanover,Germany; Riga,Camp; Transport from Hannover,Hannover,Hanover,Germany to Riga,Ghetto on 15/12/1941
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by נוסבאום ולטר
  List of Jews designated for deportation from Hannover to Riga, 15/12/1941
- Notifications by the Red Army that Red Army soldier Naum Moltyaner was Missing In Action in battle, 1944 and that Red Army soldier Abram Abramov was Missing In Action, 1942, 25/10/1947-25/05/1948; 7 Certification Letter Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/625
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by אברמוב ילנה
  Notifications by the Red Army that Red Army soldier Naum Moltyaner was Missing In Action in battle, 1944 and that Red Army soldier Abram Abramov was Missing In Action, 1942 - Additional documentation regarding their being Missing In Action; Included in the file: Letter by Naum Moltyaner to his wife Fanya, who had been evacuated to Uzbekistan; letter dated, May 1943.
- Family tree of Avraham Lazar, from Greece; some family members perished during the Holocaust, date empty; 3 List of murdered persons Genealogy Original; O.41/629
  Genealogy; <>,<>,<>,Greece
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by לזר אברהם
  Family tree of Avraham Lazar, from Greece; some family members perished during the Holocaust
- Jewish National Fund (JNF) documentation regarding the planting of trees in memory of members of the Popiski, Katz and Giterman families from Swieciany and the vicinity who perished in the Holocaust, date empty; 5 Personal documents Record of murdered persons Original Handwritten; O.41/633
  Commemoration; Swieciany,Swieciany,Wilno,Poland; Nowe Swieciany,Wilno,Wilno,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by כץ רבינוביץ מרים\3
  Jewish National Fund (JNF) documentation regarding the planting of trees in memory of members of the Popiski, Katz and Giterman families from Swieciany and the vicinity who perished in the Holocaust
- Partial list of Jews from Rovno who were murdered, near Sosenki, 06-09/11/1941, date empty; 75 List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/600
  Rovno,Rowne,Wolyn,Poland; Sosenki,forest,Murder Site
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by וייצר אליהו
  Partial list of Jews from Rovno who were murdered, near Sosenki, 06-09/11/1941
  The list/s contain approximately 2400 names
- Documentation including excerpts from a list of Jews from Tarnow designated for deportation, 19/08/1942-14/09/2000; 6 Personal documents Certification List of deportees List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/677
  Tarnow,Tarnow,Krakow,Poland; Pilzno,Murder Site
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Adler Leib
  Documentation including excerpts from a list of Jews from Tarnow designated for deportation Confirmation issued by the Head Commission for the Prosecution of Crimes against the Polish Nation regarding the fate of Joel Adler who was murdered by the Germans along with other Jews in the Pilzno Jewish cemetery, 12/06/1942
  - Sections from a list of Jews from Tarnow intended for deportation, 1942, 19/08/1942-19/08/1942; 2 List of deportees; O.41/677.1
    Sections from a list of Jews from Tarnow intended for deportation, 1942
  - List of Jews from Tarnow murdered in the Jewish cemetery in Pilzno, 12/06/1942, 14/09/2000-14/09/2000; 1 List of murdered persons; O.41/677.2
    List of Jews from Tarnow murdered in the Jewish cemetery in Pilzno, 12/06/1942
- List of residents of the Zhitkovichi district who perished, 1941-1943, 1994-1994; 25 List of murdered persons Print; O.41/645
  Zhitkovichi,Zhitkovichi,Polesye,Belorussia (USSR); <>,Zhitkovichi,Polesye,Belorussia (USSR); Lenin,Luniniec,Polesie,Poland; Lyudzyanevichy,Zhitkovichi,Polesye,Belorussia (USSR); Turov,Turov,Polesye,Belorussia (USSR); Zapesochye,Turov,Polesye,Belorussia (USSR); Storozhovtsy,Zhitkovichi,Polesye,Belorussia (USSR); Pukhovichi,Zhitkovichi,Polesye,Belorussia (USSR)
  List of residents of the Zhitkovichi district who perished, 1941-1943 The list was published in the book "Pamyats" in the volume dedicated to the Zhitkovichi region (Minsk: 1994).
- Notification by the Red Army regarding the fate of Israel Drutman, from Zhitomir, who was killed in action in battle, 14/12/1942, Izveshcheniye; 28/06/1950-28/06/1950; 2 Personal documents Certification Record of murdered persons Original; O.41/664
  Jewish soldiers in the Red Army; Zhitomir,Zhitomir City,Zhitomir,Ukraine (USSR); the Soviet armed forces,<>,<>,<>
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by דרוטמן ארתור
  Notification by the Red Army regarding the fate of Israel Drutman, from Zhitomir, who was killed in action in battle, 14/12/1942
- Lists of Jews from Pirot and Nis, and lists from Banjica and Jasenovac camps, date empty; 63 List of persecuted persons List of murdered persons List of refugees List of camp inmates xerox; O.41/674
  Banjica,Camp,Yugoslavia; Nis,<>,Serbia North,Yugoslavia; Pirot,<>,Serbia North,Yugoslavia; Jasenovac,Camp,Yugoslavia
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by לבל ג'ני
  Lists of Jews from Pirot and Nis, and lists from Banjica and Jasenovac camps
  - List of non-Yugoslavian Jewish refugees in Nis, 1941, date empty; 3 List of Jewish refugees; O.41/674.1
    Jewish refugees during the War; Nis,<>,Serbia North,Yugoslavia
    List of non-Yugoslavian Jewish refugees in Nis, 1941
  - List of Jews from Yugoslavia who perished in Banjica camp, 1945-1945; 22 List of murdered persons; O.41/674.2
    <>,<>,<>,Yugoslavia; Banjica,Camp,Yugoslavia
    List of Jews from Yugoslavia who perished in Banjica camp The list was first published by the Yugoslavian weekly "Glas", 1945.
    The list/s contain approximately 506 names
  - List of Jewish residents of Pirot, date empty; 4 List of Jewish residents List of persecuted persons; O.41/674.3
    Pirot,<>,Serbia North,Yugoslavia
    List of Jewish residents of Pirot
    The list/s contain approximately 186 names
  - List of Jewish residents of Nis, date empty; 6 List of Jewish residents List of persecuted persons; O.41/674.4
    Nis,<>,Serbia North,Yugoslavia
    List of Jewish residents of Nis
  - List of Jewish refugees from Yugoslavia in Nis, 1941, date empty; 2 List of Jewish refugees; O.41/674.5
    List of Jewish refugees from Yugoslavia in Nis, 1941
  - Lists of Jewish inmates in Jasenovac camp who were registered as tailors, 1942-1943, 1942-01/09/1943; 25 List of camp inmates List of skilled professionals; O.41/674.6
    Jewish experts; Forced labor; Jasenovac,Camp,Yugoslavia
    Lists of Jewish inmates in Jasenovac camp who were registered as tailors, 1942-1943
    The list/s contain approximately 183 names
- Pamphlet in memory of brothers Yosif Talvi and Isak Talvi, from Bulgaria, who were active as partisans and died in battle, June 1944, date empty; 2 Names of Jewish partisans Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/532
  Partisans - Jews; <>,<>,<>,Bulgaria; Partisans in Bulgaria
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by טלבי יום טוב
  Pamphlet in memory of brothers Yosif Talvi and Isak Talvi, from Bulgaria, who were active as partisans and died in battle, June 1944
- List of Jewish women inmates transferred from Auschwitz to Lippstadt labor camp, 23/11/1944, 23/11/1944-23/11/1944; 6 List of Jewish women List of camp inmates xerox; O.41/685
  Women prisoners; Women; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland; Lippstadt (Lipps. Eisen- u. Mettalwerke),Camp
  The reference code for of the materials at PANSTWOWE MUZEUM W OSWIECIMIU - BRZEZINCE, OSWIECIM, POLAND is Nr D-Br-3/1/4 (Nr 149720
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by רביד ברוך
  List of Jewish women inmates transferred from Auschwitz to Lippstadt labor camp, 23/11/1944
- Certifications regarding the death of Zwaaf, de Hoop and Godschalk family members, from Amsterdam, who perished in various camps, 1942-1944; certifications dated, 1958-1994, Uittreksel; 31/01/1958-30/09/1994; 9 Personal documents Certification Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/844
  Amsterdam,Noordholland,<>,The Netherlands; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland; Sobibor,Extermination Camp,Poland; Trawniki,Camp
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by גודסהלק לואיס
  Certifications regarding the death of Zwaaf, de Hoop and Godschalk family members, from Amsterdam, who perished in various camps, 1942-1944; certifications dated, 1958-1994
- Notification by the Red Army regarding the fate of brothers, Red Army soldiers Isaak, Zinovi and Illiya Pliskin, from Pushkin, who died in battle, 1942-1944, 09/10/1943-18/09/1956; 3 Personal documents Certification Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/727
  Jewish soldiers in the Red Army; Pushkin,Leningrad City,Leningrad,Russia (USSR); the Soviet armed forces,<>,<>,<>
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by רונין מיכאיל
  Notification by the Red Army regarding the fate of brothers, Red Army soldiers Isaak, Zinovi and Illiya Pliskin, from Pushkin, who died in battle, 1942-1944
- Certification regarding the deportation of Marianne Rosenwald, born in Chemnitz, from Berlin to Auschwitz, 09/12/1942; certification dated, 07/03/1994, 07/03/1994-07/03/1994; The file was created by International Tracing Service; 1 Personal documents Certification Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/840
  Berlin,Berlin,Berlin,Germany; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland; Chemnitz,Chemnitz,Saxony,Germany
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Cohn Franz
  Certification regarding the deportation of Marianne Rosenwald, born in Chemnitz, from Berlin to Auschwitz, 09/12/1942; certification dated, 07/03/1994
- List of Jews from Kuriniec who perished during the Holocaust, רשימת קדושי העיירה קורניס שנספו בשואה בשנים 1941-1944; date empty; 20 List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/824
  Kuriniec,Wilejka,Wilno,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by אלפרוביץ יהואש
  List of Jews from Kuriniec who perished during the Holocaust
  The list/s contain approximately 1147 names
- Lists of residents of Priluki who perished, 1941-1945, 1994-1994; 17 List of murdered persons Newspaper List of soldiers Typewritten copy Original; O.41/788
  Jewish soldiers in the Red Army; Priluki,Priluki City,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
  Lists of residents of Priluki who perished, 1941-1945
  - List of Red Army soldiers from Priluki, who died in battle, 1941-1945, Список уродженців м. Прилуки, загиблих в роки Великоі Вітчизняноі війни; 1989-1989; 3 List of murdered persons List of soldiers; O.41/788.1
    Priluki,Priluki City,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    List of Red Army soldiers from Priluki, who died in battle, 1941-1945
  - List of Red Army soldiers from Priluki who were listed as missing, 1941-1945, Список уродженців м. Прилуки, безвісте пропалих в роки Великоі Вітчизняноі війни; 1989-1989; 6 List of murdered persons List of soldiers; O.41/788.2
    List of Red Army soldiers from Priluki who were listed as missing, 1941-1945
    The list/s contain approximately 1100 names
  - List of residents of Priluki who perished, 1941-1943, Список жертв фашизма по городу Прилукам; 1994-1994; 8 List of murdered persons; O.41/788.3
    List of residents of Priluki who perished, 1941-1943
    The list/s contain approximately 271 names
- Information regarding the fate of the Binasch family who were deported from the Netherlands to Sobibor, 11 May 1943, 19/08/1946-11/10/1946; 3 Personal documents Certification Record of deportees Typewritten copy xerox; O.41/816
  <>,<>,<>,The Netherlands; Sobibor,Extermination Camp,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by אלדן מיכאל
  Information regarding the fate of the Binasch family who were deported from the Netherlands to Sobibor, 11 May 1943
- Confirmation by the Dutch Red Cross regarding the fate of Sara Wolf Alter, from Amsterdam, who was deported to Westerbork and perished in Auschwitz, 23/09/1942, 19/11/1948-19/11/1948; The file was created by Nederlansche Roude Kruis; 1 Personal documents Certification Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/837
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by וולמן רנה סוניה
  Confirmation by the Dutch Red Cross regarding the fate of Sara Wolf Alter, from Amsterdam, who was deported to Westerbork and perished in Auschwitz, 23/09/1942
- Personal documents of David Pincu Simovici, from Iasi, who perished on the death train that departed from Iasi to Targu Frumos, 06/1941, 18/04/1931-24/04/1959; 2 Death certificate Identity card Personal documents xerox; O.41/860
  Iasi,Iasi,Moldavia,Romania; Targu Frumos,Iasi,Moldavia,Romania
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by סימוביץ ליזה
  Personal documents of David Pincu Simovici, from Iasi, who perished on the death train that departed from Iasi to Targu Frumos, 06/1941 Included in the file: Marriage certificate of David Pincu Simovici and Pepi Olivenbaum.
- Documentation regarding the detention of Joseph Isboutsky, who was born in London and a British citizen, in the Ilag VIII POW camp in Kreuzburg, Germany, 1942-1944, 1942-1944; 8 Personal documents Questionnaire Card file Photograph xerox; O.41/815
  POWs; Foreign citizens; Kreuzburg,Oppeln,Silesia (Upper),Germany
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by איזבוצקי דוד
  Documentation regarding the detention of Joseph Isboutsky, who was born in London and a British citizen, in the Ilag VIII POW camp in Kreuzburg, Germany, 1942-1944
- Confirmations issued by the court in Budapest, Hungary regarding the fate of members of the Mueller family who perished in forced labor battalions and in Auschwitz, 06/08/1949-29/01/1957; 4 Personal documents Certification Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/856
  Budapest,Pest-Pilis-Solt-Kiskun,<>,Hungary; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by מילר יונה
  Confirmations issued by the court in Budapest, Hungary regarding the fate of members of the Mueller family who perished in forced labor battalions and in Auschwitz
- List of Jews from the Chernevtsy district who perished during the Holocaust, date empty; The file was created by Katja Rabina; 4 List of murdered Jews File; O.41/1426
  <>,Chernevtsy,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Chernovtsy,Chernevtsy,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Dzhurin,Shargorod,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Shargorod,Shargorod,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Tomashpol,Tomashpol,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Moyvka,Chernevtsy,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Babchintsy,Chernevtsy,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR)
  List of Jews from the Chernevtsy district who perished during the Holocaust
- Announcement regarding the death of Rebeka Regina Fuchs in Auschwitz, 25/02/1943, sent to her non-Jewish husband by means of the police headquarters in Vienna, 25/02/1943-25/02/1943; 3 Death certificate Handwritten, original Original Typewriting; O.41/1464
  Death certificates; Austrian Jews; Deportation from Austria; Intermarriage; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland; Wien,Vienna,<>,Austria
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by מיכאל ברגמן - Bergman
  Announcement regarding the death of Rebeka Regina Fuchs in Auschwitz, 25/02/1943, sent to her non-Jewish husband by means of the police headquarters in Vienna - Her date of birth, according to the announcement, was 16.12.1896; Note: Rebeka Regina Fuchs (nee Bergman) was married to a non-Jewish Austrian; they did not have any children; her husband had a daughter from his previous marriage; the announcement was found in his daughter's estate after her death.
- List of Jews from the Litin district who perished during the Holocaust, date empty; The file was created by Katja Rabina; 23 List of murdered Jews File; O.41/1438
  <>,Litin,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Litin,Litin,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Kozhukhov,Khmelnik,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Tulchin,Tulchin,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Ivcha,Litin,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR); Zhuravnoye,Khmelnik,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR)
  List of Jews from the Litin district who perished during the Holocaust
  The list/s contain approximately 913 names
- List of Jews from Zhabokrych who were murdered, 27/7/1941, Список граждан СССР, расстрелянных немецко-румынскими захватчиками в период временной оккупации по местечку Жабокрич Крыжопольского района Винницкой области; 21/06/1944-21/06/1944; 7 List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/661
  Zhabokrych,Kryzhopol,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR)
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by שמולביץ בת-ציון
  List of Jews from Zhabokrych who were murdered, 27/7/1941
- Documentation regarding the fate of members of the Firnbacher family from Regensburg and Ascher Panzer and Chane (Lehrer) Panzer from Vienna who perished in the Holocaust, 18/09/1942-04/04/1996; 11 Personal documents Memoirs Newspaper clippings Certification List of deportees xerox; O.41/537
  Synagogues before the war; Regensburg,Niederbayern und Oberpfalz,Bavaria,Germany; Theresienstadt,Ghetto,Czechoslovakia; Ingolstadt,Oberbayern,Bavaria,Germany; Wien,Vienna,<>,Austria; Kristallnacht Riots - 09 November 1938 - "Night of the Broken Glass"
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by ניצב רות
  Documentation regarding the fate of members of the Firnbacher family from Regensburg and Ascher Panzer and Chane (Lehrer) Panzer from Vienna who perished in the Holocaust - Partial list of the Jews of Regensburg who were deported to Theresienstadt, 23/09/1942; - Memoirs of Henry Saeman regarding the events of Kristallnacht in Regensburg and Ingolstadt; - Confirmation from the Vienna Jewish Community, 22/06/1990, regarding the fate of Ascher Panzer and Chane (Lehrer) Panzer who were deported from Vienna to the Izbica camp, 18/05/1942.
- Certification by the local authorities in Surany regarding the fate of Henrich and Etela Fuchs, deported from Surany, 05/06/1944, 08/07/1947-08/07/1947; The file was created by Miestny Narodny Vybor v Suranoch; 3 Personal documents Certification Record of deportees Record of murdered persons Original; O.41/676
  Surany,Nitra,Slovakia,Czechoslovakia
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by פוקס דוד